Nanette Julius

Email: njulius89@gmail.com | Cell: (661) 993-7831

https://github.com/njulius89 | www.nanettejulius.com/ntps://linkedin.com/in/nanette-julius/

SUMMARY

Creative problem-solving web developer with the coordinating and interpersonal skills to match. I create user friendly, visually appealing applications that are functional and organized. Strong detail, communication and leadership skills developed through teaching experience. Bilingual, fluent in both English and Arabic.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, Sass, React, Redux, Webpack, JavaScript, jQuery, Responsive Design, RESTful API, Chrome Dev Tools, GIT, GitHub, Node, Express, mySQL & MongoDB.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Guitar Center - Westlake Village, CA

Front End Developer

02/2018 to Present

- Develop, implement and maintain web interfaces and interactions using HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript, jQuery, JSP, React, Node, XML and AJAX.
- Creation of pages, promotions and other assets within the companies content management systems (Endeca, BCC, CMS).
- Developed and maintained user-facing features for companies 7 websites
- Support IT & QA in maintaining Test environment and resolving issues therein.

liveSity - Los Angeles, CA

09/2017 to 01/2018

Front End Developer

- Web developer developing in React.js & the MERN stack.
- Developing new client side features.
- Helping with various bug fixes and code improvements on front/back end

REX IT Inc. – Pasadena, CA

02/2016 to 09/2017

Front End Developer

- Designed clean, user-friendly, responsive websites/web applications.
- Ensured the technical feasibility of UI/UX designs.
- Developed new user-facing features.

Freelance – Remote

07/2015 to Present

Web Developer

- Designing websites/ web applications for clients.
- Various projects using Wordpress as well as websites built from scratch.
- <u>Technologies leveraged</u>: HTML/CSS and Javascript based coding.

Nanette Julius

- Page 2-

EDUCATION

University of California Los Angeles

Certificate, Full Stack Web Development

California State University of Los Angeles

B.A. Music

2016

APPLICATIONS BUILT

EventStay

- A front end app routing users to hotels near their desired events. Users can choose an event anywhere in the world and find the cheapest, highest rated hotels near it.
- http://nanettejulius.com/EventStay
- Position: Front End Developer

Swapr

- Full stack app for trading goods with other users nearby. Users can search for items within a set distance and arrange to meet and trade using the integrated chat feature.
- https://github.com/njulius89/swapr/blob/master/README.md (walk-thru of app)
- https://swapr-app.herokuapp.com
- Position: Full Stack Developer focusing on Front-End

Jamify

- Full Stack spotify clone app. Users can sign up for a personal accounts and listen to music as well as save and create playlists.
- https://github.com/njulius89/Jamify
- Position: Sole Developer